We
Speaker 1: know across this country that people have really lost faith in government. They feel like the system is working for somebody else. But not them, right. And they're not wrong. The political system fundamentally is corrupted. And at the core of this corruption, this deep rot, is money. We have to fight back against it, all of us. Campaign finance reform is also about who we elect. That's why we are supporting candidates across the country who will stand up to big money, who will try to end Citizens United. We are
so...
Speaker 1: So excited to announce the partnership between in Citizens United and off the sidelines today. We want to flip the U.S. Senate. We want to make sure we hold the House, so we want to elect more really good reform candidates in the House and
Speaker 3: then protect those who just got elected. What we saw last cycle was voters across the country really joining together to elect champions of reform and actually flipping the House with these champions. This is something that's about
Speaker 4: all of us.
Speaker 4: it's our democracy it is worth fighting for we're going to do important work it's also going to be fun at the same time but we need your help go to in citizens united.org or follow us on twitter at stop big money you can also go to off the
Speaker 5: sidelines.org and make sure that you see candidates who are running for senate and house who share your values and support them it's going to transform america
Speaker 6: politics and it's because
of your voice that will lead me to this